Let's see...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I-Is this Lt. Col. Roy Mustang?
My humble name is Edward Elric...
Humble?
You don't have to be so tense.
R-Right! We'll be boarding the 9:20 train bound for Central.
Roger.
Er, hold on...
There's one before that, isn't there?
Yes there is, but it sounds like it's already leaving.
Now departing! Now departing!
Get on that one.
But why?
Just hop aboard that one!
Al!
We're getting on!
Hurry!
I'm testing their luck.
Man cannot obtain anything
without first sacrificing something.
In order to obtain anything,
something of equal value is required.
That is alchemy's
Law of Equivalent Exchange.
At the time, we believed that
to be the true way of the world.
I don't get Lt. Col. Mustang.
I wonder what kind of person he is.
Brother,
am I scary?
No, I wouldn't say—
Say, there's someone strange over there!
Strange?
Marin, that's not nice. Keep quiet.
But he's funny!
For him to wear his armor inside the train,
he must really like it, huh?
There's nothing particularly strange about us!
There, you see?
She likes you! Right?
Pretty cool, huh?
There now, Marin,
that's enough already.
Looks like they're tuckered out
from too much romping around.
Yes.
I'm so glad that you've been able to travel
like this without any incident, General Hakuro.
They said that the situation to the east was unstable, but then here we are.
My, my, the higher-ups sure do take it easy.
By the way, where is
Maj. Hughes right now?
He is communicating with
Lt. Col. Mustang about that other matter.
That other matter?
Yes.
Well, I hope so...
So, you see...
Ever since my wife got pregnant,
she's been getting prettier by the day.
How should I put it?
She's like an angel who has
waltzed her way down to earth—
Huh?
We got cut off again. What lousy conditions for communications!
I can't do anything with this!
You're the one we
can't do anything with!
I'd better make another round to keep myself from worrying.
Hello?
My, my...
So, listen, what am I going to do if the baby is born tomorrow?
Hughes...
I've heard this story
about fifty times now.
If you want to talk about this,
take it up with your wife directly!
I have! Just a little while ago!
Then don't ask me!
Pardon me for breaking in.
Major, a piece of advice...
The baby won't be born after just five months!
Huh? What was that?
I can't hear too well
over this phone.
That's suspicious...
That's enough, Hughes.
We just got confirmation that there's no one monitoring communications.
So, how about it?
Have you seen anyone suspicious?
No. Or so I'd like to tell you.
There have been more passengers
getting on and off than anticipated.
If you factor in the private rooms...
What is it?
They're here!
They're here?
Someone awfully suspicious!
What?!
They're wearing armor this huge!
Armor?
That guy is fine. Is there another...
pipsqueak together with him?
Pip...
...squeak?
He was right! He's here!
And he really is little!
Who are you calling so puny that you can only make him out under a magnifying glass?!
No, I was just...
I'm not the one who said so...
Be quiet! Everyone, put your hands where I can see 'em!
Wh-Why, you...
Good day, General Hakuro.
Hey, Hughes! What is it?
Has something happened?
Hey, Hughes!
Hey, inform Bald that
we've taken the wireless!
It doesn't look like anyone was using it, either!
Is it them, after all?
There's a call for headquarters from General Hakuro
aboard the train heading for Central.
It's an emergency.
Put it through.
It's me.
Lt. Colonel? Is this Lt. Col. Mustang?
This is Bald, of the Eastern
Liberation Front "Blue Squad."
We have taken control of this train.
What are your demands?
Don't play dumb!
We suddenly lost contact with one of our allies today.
Someone who was supposed to have delivered a statement to you.
What are you talking about?
Okay, fine.
Bring our leader in
Prison No. 8 to Central Station.
We'll exchange prisoners there.
Very well. In exchange,
do not kill anyone. If you do—
Are you sure about this?
We do have a statement here,
but if the general finds out,
he's going to ask who was responsible.
No problem.
As long as the situation gets resolved, right?
I've already taken sufficient measures.
What is this man Mustang thinking?
If he does anything funny, then it won't just be you!
Consider all of the passengers dead!
Brother...
Yeah...
Hey, you two...
Why, you!
Hey, now that you've
done that, what do we do?
When their buddies come to get back at us for this...
He's right.
If you hadn't resisted, we probably would've gotten to Central without any trouble.
He's right...
What do we do?
You're asking me?
Are you all right?!
Yes...
Sorry about that. Your big brothers
will take care of this somehow, okay?
Let's go, Al.
Yeah.
Hey, you guys!
This is embarrassing.
Who on earth are you?
We're just ordinary alchemists.
Eh? Really?
I'm Falman. Warrant Officer.
A soldier? You don't look at all like one!
There's a reason why I'm dressed like this.
You see, up in the first car...
Then that's who the criminals are after?
And they're dragging all these people into the middle of it!
Al, I'll go at them from above.
You take them from below with this man.
O-Okay.
What?
Hey! Come quick!
There's something funny going on behind us!
Ah! You'd better not shoot!
I was about to tell you that you risked ricochets by shooting.
What's going on?!
Ah! You'd better not shoot!
Hey, Bald! Contact from
behind us has been cut off!
What's going on?!
So, you did have something set up, didn't you?
G-Give up already.
Turn yourselves over,
and release the other passengers.
Things aren't just going to go your way this time!
Dear!
We're the only ones giving orders here, General.
Check all of the cars
on this train again!
And examine the outside of the cars as well!
Hey, are you all right?
I'm surprised you got this far.
I'm Hughes. Edward Elric-kun, right?
Huh? Y-Yes!
I heard about you
from Lt. Col. Mustang.
From the Lt. Colonel?!
Yeah.
Now then, you'll work with me.
I've already checked things out below us.
What's the matter?
Who are you?!
There you are!
Take this!
Are you all right?!
What?!
Whoa, that was awesome!
Hey, you!
Don't mess around with the tender! It's the life of this train!
Yeah, sorry!
Tender, huh?
You can't, Bald!
There's someone outrageous up there!
Bald!
Contact with everywhere else
has been cut off!
They said something
about a big suit of armor!
Calm down!
You guys in the criminal group, can you hear me?
What's that?
All right, you guys!
Threaten everyone else, will you?!
Let the hostages go!
Are you one of Mustang's secret agents?!
If you interfere,
I'll kill the hostages one by one!
Oh, you're just itching to do it, huh?
Well, then...
A water... pipe?
Okay, hostages, please take cover!
What?!
Welcome!
All right, don't move.
You're the ringleader, aren't you?
What's the matter?
Come on out.
Damn!
Before I kill the general,
I'll take care of you!
Hold it!
A fellow Automailer, huh?
A brat like you...?
Is the military using even children now?
You'll pay for that "brat" line!
And I'm not being used by anyone!
Kid, let me tell you something.
I used to be in the military long ago.
At the time, I thought
I wanted to be better armed.
But the military didn't seem to like that idea.
They were afraid of me becoming any stronger on my own.
Shortly after I had this operation, they got rid of me.
And so... And so...
I wanted to crush the military!
You understand, don't you?
If you've got an arm like that,
then you must've wanted it too!
You wanted to be stronger than anyone else!
No, I don't understand!
And don't you dare lump my arm in...
with yours!
Good grief,
that was something else.
Don't kill anyone.
That's what I told you.
As it turns out, it looks like you did as you were told.
You're Mustang, are you?
A-Awesome!
I held back.
The effect on your body probably isn't as bad as it looks.
I am Roy Mustang.
My rank is Lt. Colonel,
and I am the Flame Alchemist.
Remember that.
He's Mustang...
Brother!
Lt. Colonel!
Why, you... You knew about all of this when you had us board this train, huh?!
It's not as if I had
a grasp of everything.
More importantly though, I have good news.
His generalship heard
about your exploits,
and he said he would
specially allow you
to take the State Alchemist Certification Exam.
Specially?
But we came because you told us to take it!
There's no way a child could take
such an important military test, you know.
Now, aren't you glad that I had you take this train?
Whether or not you take the test is still up to you.
Of course we're going to take it!
We'll take it, all right!
Apparently, those people had us
dancing right in the palm of their hand.
But then, there was no way around it.
We still don't have any power.
There he is! Over here! Over here!
Marin-chan!
Big Brother, thank you!
Thank you!
Fullmetal Alchemist...
Episode 6: "State Alchemist
Qualification Exam"
Everyone but me thinks
it's impossible for Brother to pass.
But then, on that day,
miraculous flowers will bloom.